Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
- Series XXXIV. Photographs and Slides
  - Exercise class, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Rev. Ivory Simmons (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Jenkins Family (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Miss Lena Williams (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Cora Lee Balkom (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Dijon Montpremier (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Photo shoot, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Elizabeth Herring photo at SFF, by Cornell, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Migrant Program proof sheet - University Photography, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Workers picking (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Haitians at Fowler Camp, Wolcott (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - FmHA - Funded housing in Wayne County (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Labor camps - Other counties (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - John Joyce (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Kathy (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Staff photos (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Cornell photo shoot, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Diversity workshop photos by Cornell, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Richard Witt (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Linda Lucas Browning (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Farmworkers excluded from New York State labor laws slide show, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Who Are America's Farmworkers slide show, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Slides and negatives, 1980-1985 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Slides - Teaching about Haiti (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Housing slides (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Slide script, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Migrant farmworker scripts (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Photo shoot paper, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Geneseo Migrant Center slides, 1980-1989 (Box 37)
  - Two small cases of Cornell Migrant Program slides (Box 37)
- Series XXXV. Literacy
  - Literacy program description (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Literacy photo, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Literacy classes photos, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Harvest dinner photos, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Literacy classes photos description, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Literacy celebration photos, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Literacy class photos, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Harvest dinner photos, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Jesse Jackson rally photos (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Literacy and Harvest Dinner (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Photos taken by literacy students with Cornell Migrant Program cameras, 1980-1989 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Tutoring migrants - LVA slide show, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Literacy/ESL resources materials, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Student written stories by World Education (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Literacy resources materials (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - The Cornell Migrant Program literacy and ESL program photo album (Box 30)
  - File boxes - Student volunteers and student and tutor file (Box 30)
  - Cassette tape - BOCES Geneseo Migrant Center - Tutoring migrants (Box 30)
  - VISTA - BOCES Geneseo budgets (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - VISTA - BOCES Geneseo project reports, 1988-1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - VISTA volunteer - Janice Comer (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - VISTA volunteer - Maybel Davila (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - VISTA progress report from Geneseo (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence VISTA volunteer program (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Literacy - RSVP program (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Literacy program - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Literacy volunteers of Wayne County (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Literacy coalition - Transportation issues, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Literacy project overviews (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Student recognition (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Literacy programs reports (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Tutor recruitment (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Tutors: Recognition information (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Wayne County outreach coordination (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Literacy program - Students referral forms, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Tutor student placements, 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Tutor reports, 1982-1985 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Student registration and interviews (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Student exit interviews, 1985-1987 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Glover Mason's work (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Student attendance forms, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Tutor data sheets, 1981-1988 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Student work (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Literacy program - News coverage (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Penfield High School student volunteers (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Tutors surveys (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Information on students (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Literacy Coalition - minutes, meetings, agenda's, etc., 1990-1995 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Tutor training agendas and materials, 1982-1986 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Maybel Davila reports and correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Maribel Ledezma - Summer intern, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Literacy program grants (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Creole language course, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Grants, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Grants, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Grant information, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Grants, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Grant information, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Grants, 1987-1988 Civil Rights at the United States Department of Agriculture, February 1997 Diversity Considerations for the plan of Work Process, October 1991 Racial Inequality: Putting Youth at Risk (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - The Connection - Articles, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Tutor training (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Tutor newsletter (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Tutor newsletter (Box 38, Folder 45)
- Series XXXVI. Action/Cooperative Communication Between Home and School
  - ACTION - Video production (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - ACTION - Program North Rose - Wolcott Central Schools (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - ACTION - Volunteer information (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - ACTION program - Federal materials (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - ACTION - News articles (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - ACTION program correspondence (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - ACTION correspondence activity descriptions (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - ACTION volunteers at Wayne County minority arts events (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - ACTION program Penfield High School volunteers (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - ACTION program volunteer recognition (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - ACTION program evaluation, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - ACTION program Sodus Schools (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Photo negatives (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - ACTION advisory board minutes (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - ACTION memorandums of understanding (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - ACTION program reports in general (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - ACTION progress reports (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - ACTION program budgets, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - ACTION progress reports, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - ACTION progress reports, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - ACTION progress reports, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - ACTION program grant, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - ACTION program grant, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - ACTION program grant, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School workshop proposals national migrant education outside resources to support workshops (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Outside resources to support Cooperative Communication Between Home and School Workshops (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School Cultural Diversity Issues - Additions to curriculum - Authored by Kathy Castania, 1989-1993 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - 40-28 Cooperative Communication Between Home and School - Wayne County, 1985-1988 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Parent Involment Workshop New York State Association of Compensatory Educator's Conference, 1998-04 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School Migrant Consortium - Awareness workshop, 1988-12 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Cornell empowerment group, 1984-1989 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School Migrant Tutorial Programs and surveys/contract with Genesee Migrant Program, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School article by Kathy Castalia - Prime time, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School Western New York Migrant Program (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School self assessment form (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School, New Paltz, 1989-05 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School - Rochester City Schools NRCS, 1989-11 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School, Ontario County, 1989-05 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School, Ontario County, 1989-07 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School Migrant Tutorials - Canandaigua, 1990-06 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School - Training of trainers, 1990-03-1990-04 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School - Massachusetts migrant education, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School - Oswego Migrant Tutorial Outreach Program, 1991-01-1991-11 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School - Canandaigua MEOP, 1991-11 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Home visit workshop - Migrant PAC meeting, 1991-11 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School - New York Migrant Tutorial Program, 1993-05 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Cooperative Communication Between Home and School Migrant Tutorial, 1994-03 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Series XXXVII. Substance Abuse
  - Kathy Castania's notes (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Migrant Substance Abuse Task Force (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Task force and Cornell connection (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Migrant Drug Abuse task Force - letters of support, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Migrant Substance Abuse Task Force Proposal and Concepts Papers (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Migrant Drug Task Force - minutes, agendas, notices, 1987-1990 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Migrant Farmworker Substance Abuse Project (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Restart Substance Abuse Services Proposals (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Restart Substance Abuse Services Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Perspective: migrant farmworkers substance abuse seminar, 1990-05 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Materials on Hatians and substance abuse (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Alternatives to incarceration program (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Health issues among Haitian migrant farmworkers - Research surveys (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - FASAP - Advisory board (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Western New York Farmworker Substance Abuse Coalition minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Western New York Farmworker Substance Abuse Coalition proposals (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Wayne County Chemical Dependency Provider's Consortium (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Wayne County substance abuse program, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Conference migrant farmworkers and substance abuse, Newark, 1989-03 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Drinking, Farm and Camp Life Study - Chi, 1989-1992 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Western New York Farmworkers Substance Abuse Coalition, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Research Studies and articles on African Amerericans and substance abuse (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Development of FACAD (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Grant - Wayne County Community Services to Catholic Family Center, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - (FASAP) hearing lab, 1995-06 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - (FASAP) - Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - News reports - Drugs in Wayne County, 1987-1990 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - A survey of migrant agricultural workers in Wayne County, 1994-12 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Series XXXVIII. Videos/Audiotapes
  - Audiotapes - Exhibit presenters - Engman, Colman, Daniel, Barr, Briggs, Biermayer, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Audiotapes - Exhibit presenters - Konwinski, Parra/Pfeffer, Gaenslen, Organized Labor, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - El Regreso de un Borreguero - Allen Moore and Lou Werner, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Building community - Rural and Migrant Ministry (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - A cup of cold water-Rural and Migrant Ministry (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - 330 Miles Toward Justice - Rural and Migrant Ministry (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - New Harvest, Old Shame, 1990; 1 (Box 42)
  - Migrant farmworkers in Wayne County, 1990; 2 (Box 42)
  - Jim Holt - Labor utilization, 1984; 3 (Box 42)
  - Jim Holt - Session #4, 1984; 4 (Box 42)
  - Immigration training, 1987; 5 (Box 42)
  - Immigration laws, 1987; 6 (Box 42)
  - Richard Witt - Cornell Migrant Program deans, 7 (Box 42)
  - Migrant farmworkers - Marion, 1990; 8 (Box 42)
  - New Harvest Old Shame, 1990; 9 (Box 42)
  - Milagritos Little Miracles, 10 (Box 42)
  - Expose farmworkers and substance abuse, 1995; 11 (Box 42)
  - Dairy agriculture survey - New York State, 1991; 12 (Box 42)
  - Common apple picking techniques, 13 (Box 42)
  - Modern slavery - (FASAP), 1995; 14 (Box 42)
  - Child Labor in the Fields, 1998-10; 15 (Box 42)
  - Pruning Apple Trees - Basic Concepts - Spanish, 16 (Box 42)
  - Geneseo Migrant Center Campus, 17 (Box 42)
  - Common Apple Picking Techniques - Spanish, 18 (Box 42)
  - Farmworker Pesticide Safety Program, 19 (Box 42)
  - Baldemar Valesquez - Rural Opportunities Inc. annual meeting, 20 (Box 42)
  - Nightline - Migrants in Florida during Hurricane Andrew, 21 (Box 42)
  - Pruning and training video, 22 (Box 42)
  - Pack-Out Harvesting - filmed by K. Embrey, 1980-1989; 23 (Box 42)
  - Reports A Legacy of Shame, 1995; 24 (Box 42)
  - A Cup Of Cold Water, 1996; 25 (Box 42)
  - Exclusions slide show, 26 (Box 42)
  - Apple picking film, 27 (Box 42)
  - Deacon Sweenie unedited testimony, 2000; 28 (Box 42)
  - Deacon Sweenie edited testimony, 2000; 28A (Box 42)
- Series XXXIX Cornell Migrant Program and Cornell
  - Human Ecology Forum, 1989, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Human Development newsletter: The Connection with Cornell Migrant Program articles, 1982-1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Countryman - Cornell Migrant Program article, 1982, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Human Ecology News, 1998, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Chronicles - Cornell Migrant Program article, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Magazine - Cornell Migrant Program article, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Migrant Youth - Joe, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Future of Cornell Cooperative Extenstion report, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Western New York CRD agents associations, 1981-82 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Workforce - Statewide program committee - Embrey and Milligan, 1990-92 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Work Force Program Committee - minutes and correspondence, 1990-92 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Public policy education - Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Public policy education - Cornell policies (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension - Legislative advocacy (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Deans and Engman correspondence, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Carol Anderson, 1980-1989 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Review of Cornell Migrant Program by Anderson, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Anderson letter to Bove (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Dean Firebaugh visit, 1989-09-07 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Firebaugh correspondence - Embrey, 1990-1994 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - R. David Smith, Cornell Cooperative Extension and Embrey, 1990-1999 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Deans/Extension administrators Finger Lake tour, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Firebaugh, Lund and Lacy trip to Wayne County, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Dean's meeting on Cornell Migrant Program, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Dean Firebaugh and Cornell Migrant Program Strategic Plan, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Merrill Ewert, 1992-1999 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Ewert and Cornell Migrant Program, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Migrant Program and growers meeting-Ewert, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Ewert visit to Wayne County - Smith and Swanson(photos), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Ewert - Agricultural Systems Initative, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Dean Brannon meeting, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension tour of Orange County for legislators/Engman comments, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Pawelski - Cornell Cooperative Extension concerning the Cornell Migrant Program, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Jo Swanson and Ed Harwood,Cornell Cooperative Extension and the Cornell Migrant Program, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Ewert correspondence with Cornell Migrant Program, 1999-2002 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Non-Tenured Faculty Task Force - Engman, Embrey response, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Dillard, Cornell Cooperative Extension Director, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Review Committee, 2001-2003 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Migrant Program self study, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Review Committee - Wayne tour, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Internal review of Cornell Migrant Program, 2003-06 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Cornell Migrant Program - Staff response to the internal review, 2003-07 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Review - Hamilton and Eckenrode letter, 2003-09 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Castania retirement letter, 2003-09 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Cornell Migrant Program threatened, 2004-05 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Review Committee Committee interviews, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Cornell Migrant Program massacre, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Closing of program and move to agriculture (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Applebee acting director (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Pfeffer, transition chair, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Letters to Lehman, 2004-05 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Press - Cornell Migrant Program closing, 2004-05 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Save Corbell Migrant Program actions (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - FWAC student fast and protest, 2005-03-07 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Cornell Migrant Program funeral, 2005-03-14 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Cornell Migrant Program - New director hiring, 2005-04 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Cronell Migrant Program - Staff discussions concerning response, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Land grant colleges and migrant farmworkers and the poor (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - A and E - Cultural Diversity Committee, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Spanish language materials, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Cross-cultural counseling - USDA, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Diversity with extension (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Latino studies, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Department of Human Development extension retreat, 1989-2003 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Department of Human Development and Family Studies (HDFS) external report, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Human Development extension retreat and strategic planning, 1999-11 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Human Development strategic plan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - College of Human Ecology report (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - College of Human Ecology annual report, 2001-02 (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - Student Farmworker Advocacy Coalition, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - COLA student group, 1998-2002 (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - CALS and migrant students (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - Chavez to Cornell - Student group MASA, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 73)
  - A. Rodriguez, United Farm Workers at Cornell, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 74)
  - COLA sponsored event on farmworkers, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 75)
  - Ramon Ramirez, PCUN at Cornell Migrant Program, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 76)
  - Dolores Huerta at Cornell Migrant Program, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 77)
- Series XL. Albany Day Marches/Press
  - Western New York Rural and Migrant Ministry council meeting (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Press rights, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Press, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - New York Press Rights, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - New York press rights, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - New York press, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Farmworker leadership conference at Colgate Alliance, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Farm labor - Civil rights, Rural Opportunities Inc., 1994 (Box 34, Folder 7A)
  - Albany Day - Farmworker Advocacy Coalition, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Separate and Unequal - New York's Farmworkers, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 8A)
  - CITA press, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Albany Day - Farmworker Advocacy Coalition (FAC) and Working Together Group (WTG), 1996 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Albany Day team leaders, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Albany Day team workshop, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Farmworker Albany Day - Legislative visit reports, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Albany Day, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Albany Day, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Albany Day photos and radio program, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Albany Day legislative press, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Farmworker Albany Day workshop at Eastern Stream Forum, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Albany Day team leaders workshop, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Albany Day, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Albany Day position papers, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Toilets in the field - Assembly vote, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Albany Day photos, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Albany Day press, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Timeline, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Daily News editorial #1 - New York Harvest of Shame, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Daily News editorial #2 - End Harvest of Shame, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Daily News - Hughes' letter, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Daily News - Mow's letter unpublished, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Daily News - Where is the Union Label, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Daily News - Stop Milking the Farmworkers, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Daily News - Labor Gets to Work, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Daily News - Reaping Justice, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Daily News - Schmidt and Lincoln letters, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Daily News - Farmworkers Will be Heard, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Daily News - Testimony from the Fields, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Daily News - Bruno Promises the Promised Land, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Daily News - Humanity comes to Farmworkers, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Daily News - Reaping Reform, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Daily News - Governor Pledges Better Pay, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Daily News - Pataki Joins Ranks of Reformers, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Daily News - Bruno Delivers for Farmworkers, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Daily News - Workers on Farm Get Raise, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Daily News - Idea Grows on Em, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Daily News - A Friend to Farmworkers, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Daily News - Grinding Life of a Farmworker, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Minimum wage, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Daily News - First Fruits for Farmworkers, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Daily News - Farmworker Fights Not Over/Daniel, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Daily News - Step one to Worker Pay Equity, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Daily News - Solo Fairness in Labor Laws, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Daily News - Film flan man, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Daily News - Hearing Spotlight Workers' Plight, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Daily News - Polk Award for crusading editorials, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Daily News - Planting Seeds of Reform, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Daily News - Farmworker Hit Pay Dirt, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Daily News - A Capitol Plan, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Albany Day team leader training, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Timoteo Martinez poem (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Albany Day, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Legislative campaign press, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Albany Day photos, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - The Voice - Journal, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Daily News - Day of Decision for Bruno, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Daily News - Farm Workers Wait for Bruno's Nod, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Daily News - Clash in Albany Over Labor Bills, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Keep Working for Farm Workers, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 67)